저 잔혹함은 무엇일까요?
What is that atrocity?
우리가 아일랜드 포르노 회사라고?
What are we, an Irish pornography company?
난 우리가 \"피리 부는 사나이\"라는 이름을 대신할 거라고 생각했어요.
I thought we were gonna replace the name "Pied Piper."
장소 홀더인 줄 알았는데
I thought it was a Place Holder.
\"PlaceHolder\"는 솔직히 PiedPiper보다 더 좋은 이름일 것이다.
"PlaceHolder" would honestly be a better name than Pied Piper.
리처드, 난 사실 사람들에게 내가 공동 창업자라고 말하는 걸 미뤄 왔어요
Richard, I've actually been holding off telling people I'm the co-founder
'피리 부는 사나이'의 노래를 부른 건 솔직히
of "Pied Piper" because frankly,
조금 부끄러운 일이지요.
it's a little embarrassing.
다시 한번 말씀 드리지만, 당신은 공동 창업자가 아닙니다.
Well, um, just to remind you, you are not the co-founder.
그러니 아무에게도 말하지 마세요.
So please don't tell anyone.
리처드, 아비아토를 맡아요 내가 찾은 이름이 아니라 날 찾은 이름이야
Richard, take Aviato. That's not a name I found, it's a name that found me
환상 탐색을 하고 있어요
on a vision quest.
네가 해야 할 일이야
Something that you should do.